zo very generally ja ma mère natural
sound is working on a warm and quality
met mijn research nou is focused very
much van plastic pollution and so that
makes it very much about
ja in broeder naar understanding
transport nv processes at risk
en dan speciaal ecological wrists de
rotzooi oem nl ik ben cations
of course also teaching
working with other researcher phd
students is voor de science
het is ja het is het is mainly plastic
researcher metingen key feature op widow
is trying to understand 60 zo wifi en
leek als een system
river of en warm net ook appartments
nl er aos many processies koningen
system zoiets de holder i would like you
to understand zo in moskou reisde part
about mobile development of you grow
festival
bright zo is always a far cry to
understand a system en captured en de
behaviour of een system in a mobile and
then use the modeling
zo ja to make predictions
[Muziek]
bedoel zou die is models and measures
can inform experiment zo week en design
experiment whether you use mobile
simulations
ja dat mixen en is empathie die profiel
emmy lots of people scientist and some
scientists are interested in my cup of
tea pollution
deathstroke yes ze zat invloed en chill
work het zal m in wat de like working in
the field of iemands kant aan jan
huizing kit
ja maar university hij zou hij zijn mond
hou het is science for impact
nou het is vis naar je wel cadetten
motto is of course very valuable to be
able to do something which mathers dat
de artsen cycle questions that you can
try to answer that you can contribute to
that zo dus
ja daar is deurs sun beauty en doen net
met rits also very motivating op korsten
just sold in a puzzle and this topic has
both
sites in dit plastic pollution just for
scientific ooit of us very interesting
it's very complex was ook verschijnt is
met at the same time it zowel hem zo
many people at questions about te kammen
hou ik een soul wit
en wat is de best way to tackle the
issue and includes policy mythische kost
right net stroop yes boxsprings is niet
lee om to talk about you were canaria zo
not only a un m in science is 2 uur of
zo
mcp the facility in the international
science of ice-world wanneer komt ie
microplastics zijn wanneer voor tweet
dat uw en de world health organization
en cpm european commission would van
mist
asics appia dat wij world health
organization en gsm aan de mast nummer
duel no one's hij ving en zo'n design
with a group of scientific exports that
provides advice to the united nations is
tunnel site je perspectief marine war
middel perfection
bij rossem benen volgt in advising the
dutch ministry of endearment for
instance
en nou of sorry volgens in advising de
stevige calif publiek er implementing
mijn colleges voor wat quality met
perspectief michael plastics en wij niet
actual assessment of de wissers zo ik
denk de spar zijn test en many people
having
talking about how to assess your risk we
dit was van de vier werken perfecte zo
is farrazijn know this is the first risk
assessment dan corpulent maar enkele toy
bonnie ja toen richard standards
interesting zo finally putting in te
praktisch theorie te ep de welving
ja exact liefdes is dit is exact liever
zondag dus zijn tippen concept that
zijn this world wide bedoel zou our
group
en wij die spons apps can be used in een
risk assessment
er is dit is no very straightforward and
doe ik this actually also means there i
machi wow team werden the sunsets
mixinstijl namibië guide ook impact is
en de heb net een been en valuator or
maybe even criticise bij mijn positie
weekers
so some times de site is museum juni
very detailed measurements for very
laborious breed hoe
ss certain aspects witch en black is is
not feasible of het spoor technologie
monitor
zo zal is het balance sheet ring en won
ik de nobel de titel en de day-to-day
vice binnen die
en onze kost resources mij wilde air
flights and this is my blog hipster rood
hier vandaag heeft een framework je team
building val policy make it is actually
en u heeft een draai zodat je woede die
avatar really would ask you out it's the
question of communicating brisk
toe nam sciences policymakers and others
zo mijn trucs en suppose i make a must
see
oké wat ouder is post by marc plus
explosion
what they say is er een simpel reply ja
hij got this question alle
en zo ja msc ajax ontzorgen stemmen
rebuy en eet hij is
ja en aan sir de sf wel steeds je zou de
vesting hij moet say is that the bands
en mijn moeder
explain that with is de rudder en die
kubus notion ik wiens
de functies in de maïs of the four
people mijn daar namelijk spleen that
ja wat moet de per ik ben haar stem zal
friskies er idee vindt of wat many site
is een de stijn truc is in my thoughts
and testing bright zo
uiting tijd in society is more like
anything that interacts or maybe harms
santing het people value is dan time's
perceive this with oké zo is het voor in
stuk plastic tas not look night on a
beach for people see plastic floating in
the ocean
bij viel net een stip snap chestnut
bright en die valuation they have
passion for nature barry allen en zo die
stoel things de loods
doen dat fit together and then this
notion of red and adverse effects is
very very easy and very easily popzender
mines
en waar er in de natural sciences en of
zal in vorm of bezoekers of risk
assessment
dit is het warmer technical coach
daarmee het say that dit is de doos het
mixen poison
en zo en die jij me kool of plastic is
not
toxic borst safe inherent lee motten
merking en zo is een shirt en dozen
above which
chemical or wat plastic koelkast en
firth facts en of zo
ik juich beyond ik dood ben ja beetje
die ik mijn still be safe zo ledger very
different
is plastic floating in the ocean en
familie dat is not necessarily kon zo
fris toe door de is een sitter
ik de consecration charlo zal uw gasten
poesjkin situation ipad dikke top with
the danube captur tip vind om te
standings of dresscode voor comprenant
respect
seoul radio nature lovers 6 lokken van
working on the beach and the mighty
plastic bottle
floating in de selectie wel dat samsung
en concerned about something like een
serie b-bewust
britten scientist and comes back een
side wel absolute edgar snotteren
stickers de scientific since early
concerned with de level de politie after
which the four tops ik jullie had zo'n
pdf connexions op veluwe
communications wat moet u wel laat
hoi bart ik het very important deed het
toch maar als de vriend
people play in this hol discussion
de jaguar referring to
zou ik denk dat de politie dit konden
dish en
policymakers het wise and politicians
bij basically hebt de responsability
door overschie hebben zingt en to take
into account the economic interest
other interests and nature conversie kon
ze feestje en ons zo zand zijn dikke
coghlans
dare to create the ecological is zo werk
some animals of doe mijn helft hoe die
effect het mijn make-up is het zou ik
snap oliën maak de snapshot zijn zus
motiveert het with getting the art eye
refresh de blog bike and is part of the
more important for for politician
sowieso niet eens lol lol met zijn
display haitink
in advising on this well defined part of
de whole story